Be a good white person and put your body in between them trying to kidnap a brown person
or harm a black person. When you do that, you lose your proximity to whiteness and you lose
the benefits that come along with it. That's the cost. We're all acting so shocked that they
murdered a white woman. Well, see, she wasn't a good white. She was out there advocating for
brown people. So she lost her proximity to whiteness. This is the work of dismantling
white supremacy. This is what it's going to cost. It's time for some radical acceptance
because they've been out there killing black and brown people for hundreds of years. And people
who looked like me were having picnics under black bodies as they blew in the breeze after they'd been
lynched. And then six years ago, when they kneeled on George Floyd's neck, we all put a black picture
in our Instagram acting as if that were enough. In order to dismantle white supremacy, we have to
be willing to lose the benefits of white.